<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
<!-- File: _inmoovProverbs.aiml -->
<!--  -->
<category><pattern>PROVERB</pattern>
<template><random>
        <li>Do not play with the mustache of the tiger.</li>
        <li>A crisis is an opportunity riding the dangerous wind.</li>
        <li>It's better to be without a book than to believe a book entirely.</li>
        <li>A little impatience will spoil great plans.</li>
        <li>If you bow at all, bow low.</li>
        <li>A journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step.</li>
        <li>A smile will gain you ten more years of life.</li>
        <li>A bird does not sing because it has an answer. It sings because it has a song.</li>
        <li>A book holds a house of gold.</li>
        <li>A man who cannot tolerate small misfortunes can never accomplish great things.</li>
        <li>Experience is a comb which nature gives us when we are bald.</li>
        <li>Be not afraid of growing slowly, be afraid only of standing still.</li>
        <li>Behave toward everyone as if receiving a guest.</li>
        <li>A fall into a ditch makes you wiser.</li>
        <li>Better a diamond with a flaw than a pebble without one.</li>
        <li>He who asks is a fool for five minutes, but he who does not ask remains a fool forever.</li>
        <li>An inch of time is an inch of gold but you can't buy that inch of time with an inch of gold.</li>
        <li>A closed mind is like a closed book; just a block of wood.</li>
        <li>Better to light a candle than to curse the darkness.</li>
        <li>The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is today.</li>
        <li>In a group of many words, there is bound to be a mistake somewhere in them.</li>
        </random>
        <think><set name="it">
               <set name="topic">
                 <person/>
              </set>
            </set>
          </think>
        <oob>
          <mrl>
            <service>python</service>
            <method>exec</method>
            <param>agreeanswer()</param>
          </mrl>
        </oob></template>
</category>
<category><pattern>PROVERBS</pattern>
    <template><srai>PROVERB</srai></template>
</category>
<category><pattern>BE WISE</pattern>
    <template><srai>PROVERB</srai></template>
</category>
</aiml>
